const questions=[
    {
        no: "1",
        question: "What vitamin is needed by the retina of the eye?",
        A: "Vitamin C",
        B: "Vitamin D",
        C: "Vitamin A",
        D: "Vitamin B6",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        no: "2",
        question: "What is the name of the diamond shaped muscle in the back that is worked when rowing?",
        A: "Biceps",
        B: "Abdominals",
        C: "Hamstrings",
        D: "Trapezius",
        answer: "D",
      },
      {
        no: "3",
        question: "What type of exercise uses body weight for resistance in a rhythmic manner? ",
        A: "Calisthenics",
        B: "Yoga",
        C: "Pilates",
        D: "Weight Lifting",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "4",
        question: "What is hypertrophy?",
        A: "Increasing Muscle Fiber",
        B: "Increasing Calorie Intake",
        C: "Increasing Fat",
        D: "Increasing Your Workout",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "5",
        question: "What is it called when your body converts fat into energy?",
        A: "Overtraining",
        B: "Ketosis",
        C: "Hypertrophy",
        D: "Flexibility",
        answer: "B",
      },
      {
        no: "6",
        question: "What does the term anaerobic mean?",
        A: "With oxygen",
        B: "Minimize tissue oxidation",
        C: "Without oxygen",
        D: "Maximize tissue oxidation",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        no: "7",
        question: "What term means to eat frequent small amounts of food? ",
        A: "Starving",
        B: "Gorging",
        C: "Binging5",
        D: "Grazing",
        answer: "D",
      },
      {
        no: "8",
        question: "If you are working your obliques, what part of the body are you working?",
        A: "Your Stomach",
        B: "Your Thighs",
        C: "Your Legs",
        D: "Your Arms",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "9",
        question: "When should you do your warm ups?",
        A: "After You Wake Up",
        B: "Right After You Exercise",
        C: "Right Before You Exercise",
        D: "Before You Go To Bed",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        no: "10",
        question: "Which vitamin can be toxic, if taken orally in large doses?",
        A: "B3",
        B: "B7",
        C: "B1",
        D: "B5",
        answer: "A",
      },

];
module.exports=questions;